Guide to the Lewis Walpole Library, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Lewis Walpole Library, Yale University, records
1979-1997
RU 787
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.75
(3 boxes)
The materials consist of administrative records and photographic negatives of the Yale Lewis Walpole Library and its print collection.
Lewis Walpole Library
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-D (YRG 32-D), Records of Yale school and departmental libraries and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of administrative records and photographic negatives of the Yale Lewis Walpole Library and its print collection.
Negatives (photographs); Lewis Walpole Library
- Negatives of Walpole Library and its print collection, 1979; Accession 1992-A-029 (Box 1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted to office of origin only.
- Lewis Walpole Library records, circa 1980-1997; Accession 2009-A-003
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2033.
  - Acquisitions (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advisory CTTEE/Research and Publications (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Automation (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Background Info (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Requests (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - BOM Misc. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Budget and Investments (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Caretakers (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Day Museum (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Director (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Exhibit, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Farmington (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fellowships (general), 1990-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16-23)
  - Financial Information, late 1980's (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Fire Alarm (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Furniture (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Gifts (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - HVAC (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Jarrett (Box 1, Folder 29-30)
  - Jestin (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Lecture - Ackroyd (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Lecture- Annan (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Lecture- Butler (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Lindsay (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Lecture- Porter (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Lecture- Stone (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Lewis Personal Papers (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Librarian Search - General (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Loans (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Librarian Search- Candidates (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - LWL- New Gallery ofArt Neighborhood (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Mechanical maintenace company (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Painting (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Paintings (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Paintings-conservation (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Perissions (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Photoduplication policy (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Plates and prints collection (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Prints brochure (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Program (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Lewis Walpole Library exhibition posters, 1990s; Accession 2010-A-024
  - Lewis Walpole Library exhibition posters, 1990s (Box 1)